https://www.napo.net/page/privacy_policy

National Association of Productivity and Organizing Professionals (NAPO)
Members Only/POINT | Contact Us | Sign In
Toggle navigationMENUFind a Pro How to Hire a ProfessionalProfessional DirectoryAbout About NAPO HistoryAwardsAffiliatesGovernance Board of DirectorsByLawsCode of EthicsNAPO Antitrust PolicySocial Responsibility NAPOCaresScholarship FundStaffMembership Join NAPO ProvisionalProfessionalAlliedMulti-Person BusinessEmeritus/RetiredStudentChaptersSpecial Interest GroupsBecome a Business PartnerConference NAPO2021 Call for PresentationsEducation NAPO Online CoursesProfessional Practices CourseworkSpecialist CertificatesLogin to NAPO UniversityCertification About Certification BCPO® HandbookBCPO® BoardBCPO® StaffLogo Misuse, Ethics Complaint Become CertifiedRemote ProctoringAnnual Maintenance Fees Recertification CPO® EmeritusCurrent CPOsResources Job BoardGetting StartedResearchStatistics DatabaseMedia Media Press KitBlogPodcast
Edit This Favorite
Name:
Category:
Share:
Yes
No, Keep Private
Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which NAPO collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the www.napo.net website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by NAPO.
Personal identification information
We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, respond to a survey, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, phone number. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personal identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.
Non-personal identification information
We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about a User’s means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.
Web browser cookies
Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.
How we use collected information
NAPO may collect and use User’s personal information for the following purposes:
To improve customer service
Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.
To personalize user experience
We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.
To improve our Site
We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.
To send periodic emails
We may use the email address to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include association news, updates, related product or service information, etc.
To provide targeted services and content
How we protect your information
We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.
Sharing your personal information
We do not sell, trade, or rent User’s personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.
Third party websites
Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.
Changes to this privacy policy
NAPO has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.
Your acceptance of these terms
By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed as your acceptance of those changes.
Contacting us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:
NAPO
1120 Route 73, Suite 200
Mt. Laurel, NJ 08054
856-380-6828
www.napo.net
napo@napo.net
Last updated: May 23, 2018
Member Sign In
Remember Me
Forgot your password?Create non-member account
NAPO Updates
more
4/7/2017Attend NAPO2017 virtually!
11/10/2016Updates to The Container Store's NAPO Rewards Program
Education Calendar
more
The upcoming calendar is currently empty.Click here to view past events and photos »
Featured Members
New NAPO Members!
K. RollandA. SteinbergS. ReissM. GrahamM. HerzogJ. McLeanJ. AudreysC. BrownK. CovaruK. GarciaR. KempN. SawaiV. PINHEIROJ. HackE. CombsJ. FudgeY. de la Torre (de la Torre)S. HagaC. HuangW. GaborA. HarrisV. ReyesW. SanderJ. PeterkoS. Kaye (Booher)I. SemperJ. DuncanR. Booth (Harrington)J. EasterlingH. Bourquin
Online Surveys
Privacy | Terms of Use | FAQs | Code of Ethics
1120 Rt 73, Suite 200, Mount Laurel, NJ 08054 Ph: 856.380.6828 | napo@napo.net
© 2015-20 National Association of Productivity and Organizing Professionals. All rights reserved.
Membership Management Software Powered by YourMembership  ::  Legal
